Because I said so
因为我说过
I've never made a villain
我从来没有做过反派
I don't know
我不知道
Portions
部分
Ok
好
Virgin olive oil
初榨橄榄油
Primary fuels like you put the master there
像您一样将主燃料放到那里
I know it's a setup look like
我知道这是一个设置看起来像
I'm going to beat up
我要殴打
Mustard or whatever sinking to the bottom of the Milky Way
芥末酱或任何沉入银河系底部的东西
Terrible
可怕
I have no idea
我不知道
How to make a vinegar
如何做醋
OK Google is a 6 to 1 ratio 6 oil 1 vinegar
I prefer 2 to 1
我喜欢2比1
Start Waze
开始位置
One spoon of Mr
一勺先生
Take some vinegar
喝点醋
Do some extra virgin olive oil
做一些特级初榨橄榄油
Try to mix the vinegar and B12 together
尝试将醋和B12混合在一起
Slowly
慢慢地
Dressing doesn't separate
敷料不会分开
Amazon
亚马逊
Everybody taste
每个人的味道
If you love you
如果你爱你
Go home
回家
Ok so we're going to do is make a x a great here to start with a good amount of oil now I'm not really
好吧，我们要做的是在这里加一个x，从大量的石油开始，现在我不是真的
Specifically measuring this year but when you're aiming for it
专门测量今年，但当您瞄准时
About a 3 to 1 ratio
大约3：1的比例
Oil to vinegar
油醋
Measuring cup
量杯
And my vinegar is going to record into the bowl
我的醋要倒进碗里
Dijon mustard here and mustard seeds are really good
加芥末和芥末籽真的很好
Emulsifier that means that they're really good at holding two things that don't want to go together
乳化剂意味着他们真的很擅长将两种不想在一起的东西拿走
Together
一起
Not the first thing I'm looking forward my babe is it is really well blended in the Formula so sort of going
我最期待的宝贝不是第一件事，它确实很好地混入了配方奶粉，所以
A visual indicator to make oil into the mixture
可视指示器，使油进入混合物
And I want to be with me constantly as I had
我想像以前一样一直与我在一起
If you noticed that you're mixing balls moving around a little bit while whisking just take a kitchen towel
如果您发现搅拌时搅拌的球混合了一点点，只需拿一条厨房毛巾
Slightly damp that's helpful too
稍微潮湿也有帮助
Big lorry
大货车
I can put my mixing boring here and another word for getting away from me while I'm so whiskey
我可以把我的混音无聊放在这里，而另一个词则是我威士忌般的远离我
Oil into the boss
进老板的油
In the key here is to go slow the entire time
这里关键是要一直走慢
That's it
而已
Taste
味道
Call boy
If you were looking for a dressing that has exclusively the taste of mustard was also feeling intensely
如果您正在寻找一种仅具有芥末味的敷料，那也会给人以强烈的感觉。
Can I recommend
我可以推荐吗
Where's vinegar I just made
我刚在哪里醋